<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<schedule>
<version>2.0</version>

<conference>
<acronym>Pass the SALT</acronym>
<title>Pass the SALT 2018</title>
<start>2018-07-02</start>
<end>2018-07-04</end>
<days>3</days>
<timeslot_duration>00:20</timeslot_duration>
</conference>

<day date="2018-07-02" end="2018-07-02T17:50:00+02:00" index="1" start="2018-07-02T14:00:00+02:00">

<room name="Amphi MIGEON">

<event guid="fffff16-e594-0109-2016-ffff-ffffffffffff" id="594">
<date>2018-07-02T14:00:00+02:00</date>
<start>14:00</start>
<duration>00:15</duration>
<room>Amphi MIGEON</room>
<recording>
<license>Creative Commons by SA</license>
<optout>false</optout>
</recording>
<title>Launching talk</title>
<subtitle/>
<track>Misc</track>
<type/>
<language/>
<abstract>General informations about the conference
</abstract>
<description/>
<logo>https://conf.qtcon.org/assets/qtcon.jpg</logo>
<persons>
	<person>The organization team</person>
</persons>
<links>
</links>
<attachments>
</attachments>
</event>

<event guid="fffff16-e593-0109-2016-ffff-ffffffffffff" id="593">
<date>2018-07-02T14:15:00+02:00</date>
<start>14:15</start>
<duration>00:35</duration>
<room>Amphi MIGEON</room>
<slug>1</slug>
<recording>
<license>Creative Commons by SA</license>
<optout>false</optout>
</recording>
<title>Debian security team: behind the curtains</title>
<subtitle/>
<track>Linux Distribution Security</track>
<type/>
<language/>
<abstract>This talk will presents the Debian security team: the people, the roles, the workflows. It will also detail the handling of vulnerabilities, both public and private/embargoed ones. 
</abstract>
<description>
</description>
<logo>https://2018.pass-the-salt.org/img/salt-512.png</logo>
<persons>
<person>
	Yves-Alexis Perez
Yves-Alexis is a Debian developer, member of the security team. He works at ANSSI as head of the Hardware and Software architecture lab. As such, he’s interested in platform security and the ways hardware and software interactions are relevant to security. More specifically, he’s interested in how devices can influence the security of the platform as a whole.
</person>
</persons>
<links>
</links>
<attachments>
</attachments>
</event>

<event guid="fffff16-e594-0109-2016-ffff-ffffffffffff" id="594">
<date>2018-07-02T14:15:00+02:00</date>
<start>14:50</start>
<duration>00:35</duration>
<room>Amphi MIGEON</room>
<recording>
<license>Creative Commons by SA</license>
<optout>false</optout>
</recording>
<title>r2frida - Better Together</title>
<subtitle/>
<track>Reverse and low level</track>
<type/>
<language/>
<abstract>
In this talk we will present Frida and Radare as separate and combined tools. Have you ever wanted to enhance your static analysis with live telemetry from a running instance of the software that you’re analyzing? Did you ever want a more visual interface for Frida to type commands instead of snippets of JavaScript? If any of the above, or none of it, then this talk is for you. 
</abstract>
<description/>
<logo>https://2018.pass-the-salt.org/img/salt-512.png</logo>
<persons>
<person>Ole André V. Ravnås (Frida developer)</person>
‎<person>Sergi Alvarez aka pancake (r2 developer)</person>
</persons>
<links>
</links>
<attachments>
</attachments>
</event>

<event guid="fffff16-e594-0109-2016-ffff-ffffffffffff" id="594">
<date>2018-07-02T15:25:00+02:00</date>
<start>15:25</start>
<duration>00:35</duration>
<room>Amphi MIGEON</room>
<recording>
<license>Creative Commons by SA</license>
<optout>false</optout>
</recording>
<title>Static instrumentation based on executable file formats</title>
<subtitle/>
<track></track>
<type/>
<language/>
<abstract>
</abstract>
<description/>
<logo>https://2018.pass-the-salt.org/img/salt-512.png</logo>
<persons>
<person>Romain Thomas (LIEF developer, Quarkslab)</person>
</persons>
<links>
</links>
<attachments>
</attachments>
</event>

</room>

<room name="B001 : D'Arsonval">

<event guid="fffff16-e594-0109-2016-ffff-ffffffffffff" id="594">
<date>2018-07-02T14:15:00+02:00</date>
<start>14:15</start>
<duration>02:30</duration>
<room>B001 : D'Arsonval</room>
<recording>
<license>Creative Commons by SA</license>
<optout>false</optout>
</recording>
<title>WORKSHOP: Introduction to Bro Network Security Monitor</title>
<subtitle/>
<track>Workshop</track>
<type/>
<language/>
<abstract>
Bro is an open-source Network Security Monitor (NSM) and analytics platform. Even though it has been around since the mid 90’s, its main user base was primarily universities, research labs and supercomputing centers. In the past few years however, more and more security professionals in the industry turned their attention to this powerful tool, as it runs on commodity hardware, thus providing a low-cost alternative to commercial solutions.

At its core, Bro inspects traffic and creates an extensive set of well-structured, tab-separated log files that record a network’s activity. Nonetheless, Bro is a lot more than just a traditional signature-based IDS. While it supports such standard functionality as well, Bro’s scripting language allows security analysts to perform arbitrary analysis tasks such as extracting files from sessions, detecting malware by interfacing with an external source, detecting brute-forcing, etc. It comes with a large set of pre-built standard libraries, just like Python.

During this two-hour workshop, we will learn about Bro’s capabilities and cover the following topics:

    Introduction to Bro
    Bro architecture
    Bro events and logs
    Bro signatures
    Bro scripting
    Bro and ELK

Requirements for the workshop:

    A laptop with at least 8 GB of RAM and more than 30 GB of free disk space
    VMWare Workstation or VMWare Player installed
</abstract>
<description/>
<logo>https://2018.pass-the-salt.org/img/salt-512.png</logo>
<persons>
<person>
	Eva Szilagyi
Eva is managing partner and CEO of Alzette Information Security, a consulting company based in Luxembourg. She has more than 8 years of professional experience in penetration testing, security source code review, digital forensics, IT auditing, telecommunication networks and security research. Previously, she was working for companies like Vodafone Hungary, Ernst & Young Hungary and Deloitte Luxembourg. Eva has master’s degrees in electrical engineering and in networks and telecommunication. She holds several IT security certifications such as GSEC, GICSP, GSSP-JAVA, GWAPT, GMOB, eWPT and eJPT. Eva is member of the organizer team of BSidesLuxembourg.
</person>
<person>
David Szili
David is managing partner and CTO of Alzette Information Security, a consulting company based in Luxembourg. He has more than 8 years of professional experience in penetration testing, red teaming, vulnerability assessment, vulnerability management, security monitoring, security architecture design, incident response, digital forensics and software development. Previously, he was working for companies like POST Telecom PSF Luxembourg, Dimension Data Luxembourg, Deloitte Hungary, and Balabit. David has master’s degrees in computer engineering and in networks and telecommunication and a bachelor’s degree in electrical engineering. He holds several IT security certifications such as GSEC, GCED, GCIA, GCIH, GMON, GNFA, GMOB, OSCP, OSWP and CEH. David speaks on a regular basis at international conferences like Hack.lu, BruCON, Hacktivity, Nuit du Hack, BSidesBUD, BSidesLjubljana and he is member of the organizer team of BSidesLuxembourg. He occasionally blogs about information security at jumpespjump.blogspot.com.
</person>
</persons>
<links>
</links>
<attachments>
</attachments>
</event>

</room>

</day>
</schedule>


<event guid="fffff16-e594-0109-2016-ffff-ffffffffffff" id="594">
<date>2018-07-02T14:15:00+02:00</date>
<start>14:15</start>
<duration>02:30</duration>
<room></room>
<recording>
<license>Creative Commons by SA</license>
<optout>false</optout>
</recording>
<title></title>
<subtitle/>
<track></track>
<type/>
<language/>
<abstract>
</abstract>
<description/>
<logo>https://2018.pass-the-salt.org/img/salt-512.png</logo>
<persons>
</persons>
<links>
</links>
<attachments>
</attachments>
</event>
